bingohideout.co.uk 2016-11-05

# Privacy Statement and Terms and Conditions | Bingo Hideout

## Privacy Statement

Bingo Hideout has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and security. It is our policy not to sell, exchange, or release ANY of your individual personal information to a third party without your expressed permission. Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Some sites use this for marketing. We don't. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your preferences and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the forum.

Bingo Hideout complies with the standards, procedures and requirements laid down by the UK Data Protection Act 1998, to ensure that the personal information you provide is kept secure and is processed fairly and lawfully. No personal information is publicly accessible.

##### External Websites

This site contains links to other sites. Bingo Hideout and affiliates are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. These sites makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to  users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Bingo Hideout has advertising banners provided by external companies, these ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by external companies, and we do not have access to this information. While these cookies do not contain personal information, you can disable cookies if you so choose. See your browser's help file for more information. Bingo Hideout recommends that users carefully check the privacy policies of the external sites that Bingo Hideout links to in order to determine exactly what details the sites hold on record and how these sites handle credit card information. Bingo Hideout is not responsible for the policies of external sites.

##### Email Addresses

Bingo Hideout Members will receive email communication from the site. If the customer does consent to receive email from Bingo Hideout, Bingo Hideout agrees to have a simple unsubscribe option available, along with unsubscribe instructions in every email.

Bingo Hideout will never share your details with 3rd party companies but websites owned and operated by Solid Digital Marketing Ltd (Owner of Bingo Hideout) may use your details for marketing purposes.

##### eCOGRA

Bingo Hideout supports the work of eCOGRA the leading independent standards authority for the online gaming industry. A non-profit organization, eCOGRA helps players identify online gaming sites that are safe, fair and responsible.

##### What Does The eCOGRA Seal Mean?

The Play It Safe Seal is awarded to operators that fully comply with eCOGRA's strict standards for player protection, fair gaming and responsible operator conduct. Sites and their player policies are checked and rechecked on an ongoing basis to ensure their compliance with these standards, as well as your safety online. The Seal has become a homepage symbol of documented, objective, fair play.

eCOGRA certified sites are regulated and monitored to ensure:

  * Fair gaming practices
  * Timely and efficient payouts
  * Fast dispute resolution

eCOGRA's primary mission is to make online gaming safer for players everywhere. Always look for the Play It Safe Seal before gambling online. If a site does not carry the Seal, you might be at risk. Know that if you should ever have a problem on an eCOGRA sealed site, eCOGRA will try to help you resolve your dispute as a Fair Gaming Advocate.

##### Where Can I Get More Information?

For more information, please go to [www.ecogra.org](http://www.ecogra.org/)

##### Contacting This Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.bingohideout.co.uk/contact/bingoben.html) at any time.

## Terms & Conditions

##### Use Of Bingo Hideout

Your use of this website and any service contained within constitutes acceptance of these Terms & Conditions. By using this site, you accept these terms of use. If you do not accept these terms of use, please do not use this site.

##### Forum & Member Profiles

You agree, through your use of the forum, that you will not post any material which is false, defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, vulgar, hateful, harassing, obscene, profane, sexually oriented, threatening, invasive of a person's privacy, adult material, or otherwise in violation of any International or United States Federal law. You also agree not to post any copyrighted material unless you own the copyright or you have written consent from the owner of the copyrighted material. Spam, flooding, advertisements, chain letters, pyramid schemes, and solicitations are also forbidden on this forum.

Note that it is impossible for the staff or the owners of this forum to confirm the validity of posts. Please remember that we do not actively monitor the posted messages, and as such, are not responsible for the content contained within. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information presented. The posted messages express the views of the author, and not necessarily the views of this forum, its staff, its subsidiaries, or this forum's owner. Anyone who feels that a posted message is objectionable is encouraged to notify an administrator or moderator of this forum immediately. The staff and the owner of this forum reserve the right to remove objectionable content, within a reasonable time frame, if they determine that removal is necessary. This is a manual process, however, please realize that they may not be able to remove or edit particular messages immediately. This policy applies to member profile information as well.

You remain solely responsible for the content of your posted messages. Furthermore, you agree to indemnify and hold harmless the owners of this forum, any related websites to this forum, its staff, and its subsidiaries. The owners of this forum also reserve the right to reveal your identity (or any other related information collected on this service) in the event of a formal complaint or legal action arising from any situation caused by your use of this forum.

You have the ability, as you register, to choose your username. We advise that you keep the name appropriate. With this user account you are about to register, you agree to never give your password out to another person except an administrator, for your protection and for validity reasons. You also agree to NEVER use another person's account for any reason.  We also HIGHLY recommend you use a complex and unique password for your account, to prevent account theft.

After you register and login to this forum, you will be able to fill out a detailed profile. It is your responsibility to present clean and accurate information. Any information the forum owner or staff determines to be inaccurate or vulgar in nature will be removed, with or without prior notice. Appropriate sanctions may be applicable.

Please note that with each post, your IP address is recorded, in the event that you need to be banned from this forum or your ISP contacted. This will only happen in the event of a major violation of this agreement.

Also note that the software places a cookie, a text file containing bits of information (such as your username and password), in your browser's cache. This is ONLY used to keep you logged in/out. The software does not collect or send any other form of information to your computer.

##### Competitions

Competitions and Prize draws are open to anyone over the age of 18 based in the UK. All competitions within Bingo Hideout are free to enter. Participants are however, expected to pay their own cost of connecting to the web site, or where competitions are phone based, the cost of the phone call or SMS message.

Winners of any competition will be notified by email within one week of the closing date of the competition except where competitions are jointly offered with a third party. In this case, winners will be notified once the third party has drawn the winner. Should the email bounce, an attempt to contact the customer will also be made by phone. If contact cannot be made within one month, the prize will be lost. Prizes will be sent by default to the customers registered address. It is the winners responsibility to notify Bingo.org.uk of any change in address.

##### License

Bingo Hideout grants you a license to access the content, information and services contained within this website for personal use only. This license allows you to download and cache (using your browser) individual pages from our website. This license does not allow you to download and modify individual pages or substantial parts of our website nor to make our website available via an intranet, where our website or a substantial part of it is hosted locally on the intranet in question. The website design, layout, content or text cannot be copied, edited or otherwise manipulated without our express prior written permission. The website cannot be placed within the frame-set of another site.

##### Copyright

All content, databases, graphics, buttons, icons, logos, layouts and look & feel are the copyright of Bingo Hideout, unless expressly acknowledged as otherwise.

##### Entire Terms & Conditions

These Terms & Conditions set out the entire agreement and understanding between you and Bingo Hideout. We reserve the right to change these Terms & Conditions at any time.

##### Jurisdiction

These Terms & Conditions shall be interpreted, construed and enforced in accordance with English law and shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English Courts. Your statutory rights are unaffected.

##### Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of BingoHideout.co.uk, or require any further information, please [contact us here](http://www.bingohideout.co.uk/contact-us/bingoben.html). Please note that we can not answer inquiries relating to any product or service featured on our site.

General inquiries for Bingo Hideout can be sent by post or using our contact page.

Solid Digital Marketing Ltd  
Suite 72  
Cariocca Business Park  
2 Sawley Road  
Manchester  
M40 8BB

Company registration number: 5846823
